

BAGUS ILHAM SANTOSO

IT System and Operations

PROFILE

Saya sedang mencari kesempatan untuk mengembangkan keterampilan baru sambil memperkuat keterampilan yang saya miliki. Pengalaman saya di bagian IT selama 5 Tahun, Saya bisa bekerja dengan baik atas inisiatif saya sendiri dan sebagai bagian dari tim. Kekuatan utama saya adalah kemampuan Analisa dan Inisiatif yang tinggi untuk menyelesaikan sebuah pekerjaan. Saya mencoba mempelajari sesuatu yang baru dari setiap pengalaman karena saya percaya selalu ada ruang untuk peningkatan diri baik secara pribadi maupun profesional.

EDUCATION

STMIK Bani Saleh Kota Bekasi 2019 - 2022

Teknik Komputer - D3 **IPK : 3.60 / 4.00**

•SMKN 3 Kota Bekasi 2014 - 2017

Teknik Komputer dan Jaringan (TKJ)

CERTIFICATION & TRAINING

- MTCNA (Mikrotik Certified Network Academy)
- **CCNA 1** (Cisco Certified Networking Academy)
- NSE 1 & 2 (Network Security Expert)
- Menjadi Google Cloud Engineer (Dicoding)
- Belajar Dasar Google Cloud (Dicoding)

SKILLS

Network

- Mikrotik
- Fortigate
- Cisco

Program

- HTML & CSS
- PHP
- C/C++
- Bootstrap

Server

- Ubuntu Server
- Windows Server

Design

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XDesign

Office

- Word
- Excel

CONTACT

Telepon: ilhambagus477@gmail.com

Email: 0858-9443-9480

Portofolio:

https://bagusilhamsantoso.github.io/portofolio/

LinkedIn :

https://id.linkedin.com/in/bagus-ilham-santoso-128824163/en

WORKING EXPERIENCES

PT Intikom Berlian Mustika IT System & Operation

On Site PT BCA Digital | Mar 2022 - Nov 2022 Job Description:

- Create and Manage User Account and Computer Hostname in Active Directory
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & Desktop User
- Register and Manage IT Asset
- Support Connection Router Fortigate & VPN Forticlient
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Daily Checklist Server & Hub Room

PT Intikom Berlian Mustika - IT Support

On Site PT BCA Tbk. | Apr 2021 - Feb 2022 Job Description:

- Checking product quality Laptop and CPU
- Re-Image OS with standard company
- Install and Update Antivirus Endpoint Security
- Respond to Service Request by ticketing system
- Deploy and Configure Laptop & CPUUser
- Withdrawal of Laptop & CPU Users
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network
- Register and Manage IT Asset

PT Arhapro

Staff IT | Sep 2017 - Apr 2021

Job Description:

- Deploy and Config Laptop & CPU User
- Troubleshooting Software, Hardware, Network and Device Peripheral
- Manage Database Microsoft Access
- Configure Router Mikrotik
- Planning and Developing Infrastructure Network
- Developing Website Company (Back End & Front End)
- Register and Manage IT Asset